Tran Duy Thai - Frontend Web Developer

Date of birth December 5, 1995

Gender Male

Phone 0917074330

Email tranduythai95@gmail.com

Address Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Website Skype: demonhuntergosh

EDUCATION

2013 - 2018 Post and Telecommunications Institute of Technology Ho Chi Minh

City

Major: IT/Information System

SUMMARY

3 years working as Frontend Web Developer.

SKILLS

Programming languages	ReactJS, Javascript/ES6, Typescript, HTML/CSS
Tools & Technologies	 Redux/Redux Saga, ImmutableJS, Normalize React Router, Next.js, React hooks Jest, Enzyme Bootstrap, LESS, SCSS, Styled-components, Marterial UI, Ant Design
Work's tracking	Git, Jira, Confluence
Methodology	Agile/Scrum
os	Windows, Linux(Ubuntu)

WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2018 - April 2019 Beesightsoft

Frontend Web Developer Main responsibilities:

- Develop frontend part of projects

Recognition and Gains:

- Knowledge about frontend technologies, mindset and learning

curve

- Teamwork and communication with colleagues

June 2019 - Mar 2020	Bestarion Frontend Web Developer Main responsibilities: - Develop frontend part of projects Recognition and Gains: - Upgrade problem solving skill - Research and learning about new frontend technologies - Able to estimate user stories more accurate - Able to work under pressure - To be a teamplayer
May 2020 - Present	Atalink Frontend Web Developer Main responsibilities: - Develop frontend part of company's product Recognition and Gains: - New frontend technologies - Knowledge about coding architecture - Working with amazing teammates

PROJECTS

VAE Tenant Portal

(Mar 2018 - Mar 2019)

Customer	Australian client
Description	Management system for rental building. - Design building: building levels, draw level's blocks - Control building's facilities - Manage building's rental fees
Team size	3
My position	Frontend Web Developer
My responsibilities	 Direct communication with client and their backend-dev through slack and email Analyze client's requirement and implement features Only frontend-dev with mentor support. Integrate APIs Fix bugs Review code Dockerize and deploy frontend part to remote Linux server
Technologies used	- ReactJS - Redux - Canvas - Docker

Efeedlink

(Jul 2018 - Oct 2018)

Customer	Efeedlink
Description	Introducing and selling agricultural product's packages Introduce company products - Online payment - Create products packages

Team size	12
My position	Frontend Web Developer
My responsibilities	- Design components according to requirements Integrate APIs - Fix bugs - Review code Main Modules: - Add user's payment method - Authentication and Authorization - Packages list - Introduce page with responsive - Searching pages.
Technologies used	- ReactJS - Redux - Stripe - Lazyload

Fixle Master Admin

(Oct 2018 - Apr 2019)

Customer	Fixle
Description	Fixle Booking app. - App for chore booking: cleaning house, fixing pipeline, electricity - Includes 3 apps: System Admin management, Services Provider management, Mobile booking apps for clients.
Team size	12
My position	Frontend Web Developer
My responsibilities	Develop System Admin management - Integrate APIs - Fix bugs - Research - Review code Main Modules: - Authentication and Authorizations Searching pages Notification and jobs status in real-time
Technologies used	- ReactJS - Redux saga - ImmutableJS - Google Map APIs - Socket IO - Intercom

Vendor Portal

(June 2019 - Mar 2020)

Customer	Meperia
Description	Management system for hospitals and vendors. - Manage trading items for surgical cases between hospitals and vendors - Manage surgical cases workflow in hospital
Team size	12
My position	Frontend Web Developer
	 Development Analyze and estimate user stories Research Integrate APIs Fix bugs Review code

My responsibilities	 Training ReactJS basics. Main Modules: Chose frontend template for project (react-boilerplate). Refactor old code to new template. Authentication and Authorizations. Create and manage surgical cases. Add medical items for specific surgical cases. Searching pages.
Technologies used	- ReactJS - Redux saga - ImmutableJS - Jest, Enzyme

Atalink

(May 2020 - Present)

Customer	Companies, Businesses, Groups
Description	B2B + E-commerce + social network website
Team size	40
My position	Frontend Web Developer
My responsibilities	 Development Analyze and estimate user stories Research Integrate APIs Fix bugs. Refactor old code with new coding conventions. Main Modules: Authentication pages Searching pages. Management forms CRUD pages
Technologies used	- ReactJS - React hooks - Typescript - Redux saga - Normalize - Next.js - ReactIntl - Styled-components - Ant design